I'll be brief today, but um I can tell
you guys as impressive as he is on the
field, he he's just as impressive off
the field. And uh we're we're super
excited to have him. Mom and dad, you
guys did a great job. And so um just
really really uh pumped to have him
here. And uh really in short, Sunny
embodies everything we look for in a
commander on and off the field. So uh
really thrilled, really excited. Uh, so
please join me in welcoming Sunny Styles
to the commander family and the DMV.
>> How we doing?
Uh, just want to say something real
quick. I want to say thank you to He
made me call him AP. I like to call him
Mr. Pet. I'm going to say thank you to
AP. Um, thank you to Coach Quinn, Mr.
Paris uh for you guys believing in me,
putting a lot of faith in me. You know,
I think when I came in this building,
you guys talked about like just
scratching the surface. You talked about
how there's so much more to unlock and
uh you know, I see it. I see the vision.
I'm excited to be here. Um I've been
telling everyone this is where I wanted
to be. Um so I'm super excited to be
here and uh just can't wait to get to
work.
>> So start off.
>> Name and affiliation. All right. Uh,
Sunny John Kim, ESPN. I'm curious now
that you're sitting up here as a first
round pick, what was your reaction when
you got moved to safety and then when
did you feel you became a guy who could
be a linebacker at this level?
>> Yeah, so when I came in at safety my
first two years, uh, it's kind of what
I've been playing my whole life. Um,
switched to linebackers my sophomore
year. You know, I think when I got to
the end of my sophomore year, I really
wasn't where I wanted to be. Um, you
know, I ended up switching, sitting down
with the coach, head coach, coordinator.
Felt like it was best for the team, felt
like it was best for me. and uh you know
I was happy to do it. You know I
attacked the role, maximized the role,
just wanted to help the team win and I
think it worked out for me.
>> Hi Sunny Liam Griffin with the
Washington Times. You come from an NFL
bloodline. I'm curious, is there any
advice that your dad has given you about
this experience and the transition going
from college to the NFL?
>> Yeah, he talked a lot about finding a
vet in in the room. Uh whether it be on
my side of the ball, on the offense,
just finding a guy that you admire the
way he works and uh you know kind of
learning from him, you know, getting all
the little little nuggets from him. Um,
and just being a uh coming in with
humility and uh the willingness to
learn, open-minded.
>> Hi Sunny. Um, Nikki Jafala with the
athletic. Um, who helped you the most as
you transition from safety to linebacker
and how do you think your safety
background helps you at that position?
>> Um, I say helped me the most, I would
say coaches, then my dad. Um, spent a
lot of time watching ball with them. You
know, my dad, he got his own stuff going
on, but he'd come in the building and
watch tape with me. Um, you know,
obviously he's former linebacker, but
then, uh, coach Lord Knight is obviously
my position coach. You know, he put a
lot of belief in me. You know, when I
switched to linebacker, he texted me and
said, "You're going to be a first-round
pick." And, uh, you know, for him to say
that after like my first two years
playing safety, like it was okay. Like,
I wasn't on a projection to be that yet.
And, uh, you know, to hear that from
your coach means a lot. So, you know, I
was super happy, super happy when he did
that. And, uh, yeah, I think those two
guys are a big reason why I succeeded at
the position.
David Aldridge with the athletic.
Welcome to DC. Um, you had a great
talented defensive room at in Columbus.
I just wonder how you guys,
you and Caleb and Arll and how you guys
kind of found a niche with one another
so that you could play as a unit
together.
>> You know, I think it starts in the
offseason. Um, you know, just training
with each other, working out, getting to
know each other, hanging out outside the
building. Um, but I think, you know, at
Ohio State, we had like-minded people.
um guys who love football, love to win,
love their brothers, and uh you know,
I'm sure it's the same thing here. Um at
least from what I see from the staff.
So, um I think we have guys who are good
people off the field and like-minded on
the field. Uh good things happen and
it's easy to gel.
>> Hey, signing Donna Hopkins, Pro Football
Plus. Welcome to the DMV. Uh this has
been a long process through the combine,
through the senior day now with the
commanders. What has that process been
like and what have you learned about
yourself in that process?
>> Um, you know, for me it's been fun. Uh,
combine prep was awesome out in
California training with guys, training
with my brother, some of my teammates,
some other guys from across the country.
That was fun. Then you go to the
combine, you got get to go out there,
compete, you know, meet with a bunch of
coaches, talk ball, talk about yourself,
um, go to pro day, go on these visits,
uh, and then obviously, you know, the
draft day. Um, so it it's been fun. It's
been great. And you know, I think I
learned about myself that um I'm not
anxious for the moment. You know, I'm
excited. And you know, I think uh you
know, talking to my dad, uh you can be
excited and be anxietyfree when you know
you put the work in. Uh so you trust
that work and then get to this next
level. You know, create a routine,
create a regimen, and trust that work
and just uh trust the process.
>> Hi there, Candy Waller, Buoie TV. Um so
can you just share what this last 24
hours have been like for you?
>> Yeah. um yesterday morning just hanging
out with a bunch of family. Uh my guys
from Vayner, just soaking it all in. Um
just enjoying each other, you know. I
think uh Pittsburgh was only a
three-hour drive, so I had a bunch of
family down there and that was awesome.
Then you go to the red carpet, green
room. Um you know, honestly, everyone
asked me all day like, "Am I anxious?"
And I told everybody no. Like I was just
excited. You know, I had a feeling I
knew where I was going and it happened
just like it was supposed to. Um, so it
was a dream come true and obviously
celebrate with the family after seeing
all my other fellow Buckeyes get drafted
was awesome. You know, we think we were
all gym. We just super happy for each
other. You know, everyone ended up right
where they're supposed to be.
>> Hey Sunny, Mitch Tesler, Moneyal Sports.
Uh, with Arll going to to New York and
Caleb going to Dallas. What are thoughts
of playing those guys twice a year and
what were those uh text messages like
last night? You guys talk at all?
>> Yeah, I saw him after in the hotel. You
know, we're excited for each other.
Can't wait to get to work. you know,
obviously we're gonna get after him, so
hopefully I can see him out there on the
field.
>> Hey, Sunny. Uh, Ben, standing with the
team 980, the the scratching the surface
comment. We've heard that, you just
mentioned it a minute ago. What does
that mean to you when when somebody says
you're just scratching the surface? What
do you kind of see as the vision for
yourself?
>> Yeah, I mean, I have high expectations
for myself, you know? Um, I don't think
the goal for my career was just to get
to the NFL and that was it. Like, round
of applause. You know, I think it's it's
I'm happy to be here and I'm happy for
the moment. Um, but there's still so
much work to be done. You know, I was in
year two at the position last year. I
thought I played fairly well. Um, but I
watch myself. I know I have so much more
in the tank and, you know, in all facet
of the game. There's so much more to
work on.
>> Hey, Sunny Les Carpenter at the
Washington Post. Uh, just the way that
you're kind of, you know, the presence
you have right now and sort of the ease
that you have in this. It's almost like
you've been waiting for this day all
your life. I mean, is is that kind of
the way it is? I mean, you you do seem
and you seem last night, too, very
prepared for all of this and nothing
seems to be phasing you right now.
You know, I think I can uh attribute
that to my parents. You know, uh they
raised me the right way and uh you know,
I think I've worked for this moment um
to get here, get to this level and
exceed at this level. Um so I think
that's why I feel ready and uh no really
no anxiety or anxiousness. You know,
obviously, you know, being at Ohio
State, they develop as as men and as
players. Um so when you step into the
building, you know, we're ready to be
pros.
Sunny, welcome to Washington DC. Chad
Ricardo with Fox 5. I had to imagine
that you've envision this moment for
years and years and years. I wonder that
now that you're here, how the dream of
this moment correlates to the reality of
it. Man, I think uh being a little kid
um like the draft felt so like surreal
and um you know it was amazing you know
once you get your name called and all
those things but uh I think once I got
my name called it was like you walked on
the stage experience all that then I was
like now I'm ready to go to work like
I'm just excited I'm excited for the
next step I'm excited to get better I'm
excited to you know help this team win.
Hi Sunonny Heather Mcdana, NBC4. Welcome
to Washington. You've you've mentioned
that this is where you wanted to be and
you met with a lot of teams who said a
lot of wonderful things I'm sure about
you about themselves. Why is this where
you wanted to be? What stuck out about
the commanders?
>> Um, you know, I take it back to like
when I was coming out of high school and
uh I went to Ohio State, went in that
building and it was great people in the
building. Um, starting with Coach Day,
the whole coaching staff, other players.
Uh when I came in this building, first
person I see, Coach Noran. Great energy.
Um you could tell he's just a genuine
guy, great man. Um then I could sit down
with Coach DJ, Coach Jones, uh go talk
to Coach Quinn, uh AP, and uh it was
just great energy in the whole building,
every single person I met with. And it
just felt right. And uh that's why when
I left this building, I was like, man,
like this this is it. This feels right.
And I was hoping it was going to work
out the way it did. So, just super
excited to be here.
>> Hi, Sunny. Welcome to Washington. Skyler
Nelson from the Washington Informer.
There have been talks um about your
leadership in when you were in Ohio. How
do you plan to bring that leadership as
a rookie into this NFL locker room as
you go into the next phase of your
career?
>> Yeah, I think as a rookie, you got to
earn the respect of the guys in the room
first. So, just coming in, uh being
reliable, being consistent, um showing
up, doing my job each and every day. Um
so, I'm just going to earn the respect
of the guys around me. u make them
respect the way I work and uh naturally
you know especially if you're a Mike
Green dot guy if that's that's what the
case may be you're going to earn respect
those guys with the way you command the
huddle the confidence in your
communication all these different things
and uh to have that confidence you have
to you have to put in the preparation so
I plan to prepare at the highest level I
can so I can be out there super
confident and uh you know not let my
guys down.
Hi Sunonny. Natalie Spala, ABC7 News.
Welcome to Washington. You obviously
have tape that speaks for itself. We've
heard about the intangibles at this
point as well, but what is maybe
something we don't know about you up
until this point that you really wanted
people to know?
>> Um, you know, one of the my favorite
things about football is the brotherhood
aspect, you know, especially when you're
in college. Like there's like a hund of
hundred of us on the team and uh you
know, I take that seriously. Like when I
step into a building, I feel like
everyone's my family and I plan to do
the same thing here. Um, I think we're
all family work. I know obviously we
work together. We're co-workers
technically, all those things, bosses
and all these things, but uh, I look at
it like family. Um, you know, I love the
people in the building and, uh, plan to
get close with everyone in the building
as much as I can.
>> Sunny, going back to like the work you
put into it. What What is it that you
put like when did you start putting the
level of preparation, all that that you
felt you needed to? What things were you
doing? Um, man, I've been working since
I was a little kid out there with my
dad, my brother,
kids from my hometown, like the people I
grew up with. Um, you know, when I was
little, you just go out there and have
fun. You love football, you love
competing, going out doing drills in the
summer, racing each other. But then as I
got older, you know, talking to my dad,
talking about wanting to be in the NFL,
wanting to win Super Bowls, wanting to
have a gold jacket, and he told me like,
you have these big dreams, but like you
have to separate yourself. um like
everyone's going to practice every day,
doing the regular stuff, doing the
mandatory workouts. So, what are you
going to do to separate yourself? So, um
just always always trying to outwork the
the guy next to me, outwork the
opponent, um do the unrequired work. Um
because I think that unrequired work is
what gets you the to these uh tremendous
goals that you you want to achieve.
>> Hey, Sunny, David Harrison, locked on
and WSA9, welcome to DC. Going to finish
this off a little bit of a softball
question for you. I don't know if you've
noticed the rebranding. I know you've
been a little bit busy, but what do you
think about uh the new logos in front of
you and the new helmets and the new
threads?
>> I think it looks awesome. Uh it dropped
actually I think it was my second day on
my uh 30 visit. So, I think it looks
awesome. Can't wait to put it on. I
think I'm going to look pretty good in
the Burgundy Gold.
>> Hey Sunny, Alex from DC News Now.
Welcome to the area. Uh you talked about
how excited you were to come here, how
you thought this is where you belonged,
where you wanted to be. So, I want to
know when you actually walked through
the doors today after being drafted,
what was going through your mind? What
was that moment like?
>> I walked in the doors, the it felt like
the whole staff was out in the hallway.
It was It was awesome. It felt like uh
almost like a family reunion. Everyone
welcomed me home. Um so, it was great.
Super excited. Um like I said, when I
walked out this building a few weeks
ago, I knew this was the right place.
And I told Coach Quinn, I was like, uh
on my way, I was like, "Hopefully, I'll
be seeing you soon." So, I was glad to
be back. Did you ask them to pick your
brother on day three?
>> No, I didn't do that yet.
>> Yes, sir. Appreciate you guys.